See, this is the problem. We want repercussions for behaviors that the society in and of itself
are the breeding grounds for. You see, that's what becomes unfair. It's like the main kind
of crimes people like to talk about, like they talk about murder and violence and rape,
which make up a very tiny percent of what is actually in the criminal system or prosecuted
or regarded at all. Not because it's not hyper-present in our society, but because
our criminal system doesn't give a f*** about those things, right? But the thing is, it's like,
well, we want to punish people for rape and sexual assault and sexual harassment and all
these things, theoretically, because our system doesn't actually do it. Ask anybody who's been
the victim of these things. They will never tell you they got justice from the system,
but we do not. And we violently respond to anybody's suggestions should exactly do anything
about rooting that out in terms of how those attitudes come to be, right? We never want
a system for that. Like, hey, can I get an education system to do something about why people don't
seem to understand consent? Why you don't seem to see women as autonomous beings? Why you don't
think men can be the victim of abuse? Why all these different things? We don't want to address any of
that, but we want repercussions for playing out or manifesting the attitudes that we are teaching people.
So when we do not know how many narratives are, we will reinforce them. So how many
people don't think we can manage that a system of course are diciendo that not much
the truth or same or even when they reach out. So without them including prejudice or